{"sid": "24JK7GHOFC8X_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 334764, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 334765, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 350539]], "time_left_end": "285", "answered_time": 350539, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "285", "question_time_start": 350539, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 355816]], "time_left_end": "279", "answered_time": 355816, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "279", "question_time_start": 355817, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["calc_3", 358778], ["calc_4", 359361], ["calc_+", 360002], ["calc_8", 361187], ["calc_7", 361621], ["calc_3", 362310], ["calc_=", 362888], ["submit", 370185]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 370185, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 370185, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 374805]], "time_left_end": "260", "answered_time": 374805, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "260", "question_time_start": 374805, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 378133]], "time_left_end": "257", "answered_time": 378133, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "257", "question_time_start": 378133, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["calc_7", 381852], ["calc_8", 382294], ["calc_+", 383041], ["calc_3", 383592], ["calc_7", 384112], ["calc_+", 384838], ["calc_2", 385851], ["calc_3", 386264], ["calc_+", 386905], ["calc_4", 387475], ["calc_7", 387901], ["calc_=", 388550], ["submit", 395253]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "240", "answered_time": 395253, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "240", "question_time_start": 395253, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 398746]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 398746, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 398746, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 404850]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 404850, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 404850, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 409713]], "time_left_end": "226", "answered_time": 409713, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "226", "question_time_start": 409714, "question": "74+73", "correct_answer": 147, "events": [["submit", 413041]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 413041, "user_answer": "147", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 413041, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 413041, "question": "43+94+89+38", "correct_answer": 264, "events": [["calc_4", 416709], ["calc_3", 417266], ["calc_+", 417800], ["calc_9", 418946], ["calc_4", 419517], ["calc_+", 420368], ["calc_8", 421081], ["calc_9", 421537], ["calc_+", 422347], ["calc_3", 422863], ["calc_8", 423350], ["calc_=", 423953], ["submit", 431745]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 431745, "user_answer": "254", "user_correct": "False", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 431745, "question": "6+8+4+86", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 437139]], "time_left_end": "198", "answered_time": 437139, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "False", "score": "8"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "198", "question_time_start": 437139, "question": "7+97+23", "correct_answer": 127, "events": [["submit", 445656]], "time_left_end": "190", "answered_time": 445656, "user_answer": "127", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "190", "question_time_start": 445657, "question": "9+36+86", "correct_answer": 131, "events": [["submit", 453301]], "time_left_end": "182", "answered_time": 453301, "user_answer": "131", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "182", "question_time_start": 453301, "question": "43+168", "correct_answer": 211, "events": [["submit", 460633]], "time_left_end": "175", "answered_time": 460633, "user_answer": "211", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "175", "question_time_start": 460633, "question": "8+9+3+48", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 465054]], "time_left_end": "170", "answered_time": 465054, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "170", "question_time_start": 465054, "question": "37+337", "correct_answer": 374, "events": [["submit", 469841]], "time_left_end": "165", "answered_time": 469841, "user_answer": "374", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "165", "question_time_start": 469841, "question": "59+48", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 475553]], "time_left_end": "160", "answered_time": 475553, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "160", "question_time_start": 475553, "question": "7+19+29", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 483926]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 483926, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 483927, "question": "88+38", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 488889]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 488889, "user_answer": "126", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 488889, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 488889, "question": "9+34+49", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 498800]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 498800, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 498801, "question": "23+33", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 501995]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 501995, "user_answer": "46", "user_correct": "False", "score": "16"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 501996, "question": "73+18+36+96", "correct_answer": 223, "events": [["calc_7", 534538], ["calc_3", 535112], ["calc_+", 535729], ["calc_1", 536262], ["calc_8", 536782], ["calc_+", 537446], ["calc_3", 538030], ["calc_6", 538446], ["calc_+", 538980], ["calc_9", 539807], ["calc_6", 540176], ["calc_=", 540720], ["submit", 547316]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "117", "answered_time": 547316, "user_answer": "223", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "117", "question_time_start": 547316, "question": "8+68+43", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["calc_7", 552350], ["calc_6", 552901], ["calc_+", 553267], ["calc_4", 553789], ["calc_3", 554341], ["calc_=", 554751], ["submit", 562000]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "102", "answered_time": 562000, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "102", "question_time_start": 562001, "question": "48+644", "correct_answer": 692, "events": [["calc_4", 564284], ["calc_8", 564776], ["calc_+", 565391], ["calc_6", 565952], ["calc_4", 566446], ["calc_4", 566600], ["calc_=", 567192], ["submit", 575207]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "89", "answered_time": 575207, "user_answer": "692", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "89", "question_time_start": 575208, "question": "78+899", "correct_answer": 977, "events": [["submit", 580438]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 580438, "user_answer": "877", "user_correct": "False", "score": "18"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 580438, "question": "9+6+6+86", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 587356]], "time_left_end": "77", "answered_time": 587356, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "77", "question_time_start": 587356, "question": "7+6+4+93", "correct_answer": 110, "events": [["submit", 591866]], "time_left_end": "72", "answered_time": 591866, "user_answer": "110", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "72", "question_time_start": 591866, "question": "8+23+57", "correct_answer": 88, "events": [["submit", 599219]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 599219, "user_answer": "88", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 599219, "question": "29+84", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 603650]], "time_left_end": "60", "answered_time": 603650, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 603650, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "60", "question_time_start": 603650, "question": "8+3+6+96", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_1", 609995], ["calc_7", 610490], ["calc_+", 611025], ["calc_9", 611667], ["calc_6", 612008], ["calc_=", 612567], ["submit", 619438]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "44", "answered_time": 619438, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "44", "question_time_start": 619438, "question": "67+89", "correct_answer": 156, "events": [["calc_6", 627344], ["calc_7", 627804], ["calc_+", 628325], ["calc_8", 628876], ["calc_9", 629220], ["calc_=", 629759], ["submit", 636490]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "27", "answered_time": 636490, "user_answer": "156", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "27", "question_time_start": 636490, "question": "4+66+26", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 639864]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 639864, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 639865, "question": "4+26+36", "correct_answer": 66, "events": [["submit", 642455]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 642455, "user_answer": "66", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 642456, "question": "14+686", "correct_answer": 700, "events": [["submit", 646253]], "time_left_end": "18", "answered_time": 646253, "user_answer": "700", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "18", "question_time_start": 646253, "question": "4+6+3+49", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 650764]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 650764, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "False", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 650764, "question": "77+97+48+18", "correct_answer": 240, "events": [["calc_7", 653862], ["calc_7", 654008], ["calc_+", 654591], ["calc_9", 655482], ["calc_7", 655938], ["calc_+", 656707], ["calc_4", 657415], ["calc_8", 657891], ["calc_+", 658669], ["calc_1", 659334], ["calc_8", 659836], ["calc_=", 660445]], "used_calculator": "True"}}}}}